Guide to the Shaun Maloney Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Shaun Maloney papers, 1932-2000; 5255-001; 35.08 cu. ft. (37 units); 261 sound cassette tapes; 10 videocassettes (VHS); 1 sound tape reel; 7 sound cassette tapes (microcassettes)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
    - Subject Series
      - NW Transport, 1993 (Box-folder 9/76)
    - Miscellany, 1993-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 10/1-2)
    - Clippings, 1962-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 10/3-7)
  - Sailors Union of the Pacific
    - Organizational Features, n.d. (Box-folder 10/8)
    - General Correspondence, 1946-1951 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - General Correspondence of Others, 1948 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Minutes
      - Special Committee, 1946 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Northwest Committee for Maritime Unity, 1946 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards. Seattle, 1952 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Agreements, 1941-1953 (Box-folder 10/14-16)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1945, n.d. (Box-folder 10/17-18)
    - Financial Records, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Bulletins, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Publications
      - Black Gang News, 1951-1955 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Canadian Sailor, 1950 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Harbor (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Marine Engineer, 1952 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - Marine Fireman, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - MCS Voice, 1952 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Seafarer's Log, 1949, 1952 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - Sextant, 1955 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Seamen's Journal, 1936 (Box:oversize 34)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941-1953, n.d. (Box-folder 10/29)
    - Legislation, 1935, 1947 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - Hatch Book - Alaska Steamship Co., n.d. (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Speeches and Writings, 1945 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Speeches and Writings-Author Unknown, 1946 (Box-folder 10/33)
    - Notes, 1948 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Subject Series
      - AB Seaman Questionnaire, n.d. (Box-folder 10/35)
      - Addresses of Note, n.d. (Box-folder 10/36)
      - H.Q., 1944, n.d. (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Island Mail-India Voyage #1, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Tonnsina, etc, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 10/39)
      - Marine News and Information, 1945, n.d. (Box-folder 10/40)
    - Miscellany, 1942-1952, n.d. (Box-folder 10/41-43)
    - Ephemera, 1948, n.d. (Box-folder 10/44)
  - Mahoney (John) Defense Committee
    - General Correspondence of John Mahoney, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 10/45)
    - General Correspondence of Others, 1946-1951 (Box-folder 10/46)
    - Minutes, 1948-1950, n.d. (Box-folder 10/47-51)
    - Reports, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 10/52-56)
    - Court Papers, 1950-1954, n.d. (Box-folder 10/57-59)
    - Resolutions, 1949, n.d. (Box-folder 10/60)
    - Petitions, 1949 (Box-folder 10/61)
    - Statements of John Mahoney, 1949, n.d. (Box-folder 10/62)
    - Union Book of Joe Mattsen, 1950 (Box-folder 10/63)
    - Financial Records, 1949-1950, n.d. (Box-folder 10/64)
    - Lists, n.d. (Box-folder 10/65-66)
    - Indices - West Coast Sailors (Box-folder 10/67)
    - Manuscripts of Frank Lovell, n.d. (Box-folder 10/68-69)
    - Notes of John Mahoney, n.d. (Box-folder 10/70)
    - Publications, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 10/71-72)
    - Subject Series
      - M/V Mail-Crew Expelled, 1949-1953 (Box-folder 10/73)
      - Canadian Seamen's Union 1949 Strike (Box-folder 10/74)
      - Wage Agreements, n.d. (Box-folder 10/75)
      - Wage Agreements, n.d. (Box-folder 10/76)
      - Wage Schedules and Computations (Box-folder 10/77)
      - West Coast Sailor Index (Box-folder 10/78)
    - Case Files
      - Mahoney v. SUP, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 10/79)
      - Mahoney v. SUP, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 11/1-26)
      - Butler, Lester, 1950 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - Coombs, Norman, n.d. (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Davenport v. SUP, 1952, n.d. (Box-folder 11/29)
      - Flindt et al. v. SUP, 1948-1955 (Box-folder 11/30-35)
      - Gillard v. SUP, 1949 (Box-folder 11/36)
      - Kolence et al. v. SUP, 1952 (Box-folder 11/37)
      - Kongele, Ben, 1949, n.d. (Box-folder 11/38)
      - Kongele v. SUP, 1950-1952, n.d. (Box-folder 11/39)
      - Maloney et al. v. SUP, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 11/40)
      - McDonough et al. v. SUP, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 11/41)
      - Paff v. Dombroff, 1949 (Box-folder 11/42)
      - SUP v. Lovell et al., 1949-1951 (Box-folder 11/43)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954, n.d. (Box-folder 11/44)
    - Clippings, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 12/1-2)
    - John Mahoney Papers
      - General Correspondence, 1946-1952, 1962 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Outgoing Letters of SUP, 1948, 1952 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Intra-organizational Correspondence of SUP, 1947-1953 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Minutes - Sailor's Union of the Pacific. Seattle, 1947 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Reports, 1946-1952, n.d. (Box-folder 12/7-9)
      - Writings, 1947, 1955 (Box-folder 12/10-11)
      - Statements, 1948 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Forms, n.d. (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Agreements, 1946-1952 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Resolutions, 1952 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Bulletins, 1946-1956, n.d. (Box-folder 12/16-20)
      - Publications
        - West Coast Sailors, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 12/21)
        - Miscellaneous, 1952-1955, n.d. (Box-folder 12/22)
        - Maclean's, 1955 (Box:oversize 34)
      - Lists, 1954 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Subject Series - Mahoney v. PMA, 1962 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Applications, 1940 (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Miscellany, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 12/26-27)
      - Ephemera, 1952-1953, n.d. (Box-folder 12/28)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)
    - Organizational Features, n.d. (Box-folder 12/29)
    - General Correspondence
      - Fisher Flouring Mills Co., 1962, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12/30-31)
      - Jugum, Martin, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - ILWU Local 13 Velasquez, 1965 (Box-folder 12/33)
      - ILWU Local 19 Welfare Officer, 1963 (Box-folder 12/34)
      - Vacations, 1965 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Willows Case, 1967 (Box-folder 12/36)
    - General Correspondence of Local 19, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Outgoing Letters of Others
      - ILWU, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 12/38)
      - PMA, 1953 (Box-folder 12/39)
    - Draft Correspondence of Others, 1961 (Box-folder 12/40)
    - Memoranda, 1961 (Box-folder 12/41)
    - Minutes
      - ILWU Local 19 Minute Books, 1941-1946, 1955-1984 (Box-folder 13)
      - ILWU Local 19 Executive Board, 1970 (Box-folder 12/42)
      - ILWU Local 19 Membership, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 12/43)
      - ILWU International Executive Board, 1966 (Box-folder 12/44)
      - Conference of Arbitrators, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 12/45)
      - Joint Longshore Labor Relations Committee, Los Angeles - Long Beach, 1967 (Box-folder 12/46)
      - Pensioners, 1968 (Box-folder 12/47)
    - Indices to Coast Labor Relations Committee Minutes, 1965 (Box-folder 12/48)
    - Agreements
      - Coastwide Rules, 1984 (Box-folder 12/49)
      - Foremen's Agreement, 1950 (Box-folder 12/50)
      - ILWU/International Association of Machinists, n.d. (Box-folder 12/51)
      - ILWU/PMA, 1951-1996 (Box-folder 12/52-75)
      - ILWU/Western Conference of Teamsters, 1961 (Box-folder 12/76)
      - ILWU/Seattle Stevedoring Co., 1975 (Box-folder 12/77)
      - ILWU/Northland Marine Lines, 1976 (Box-folder 12/78)
      - ILWU Canadian Area/B.C. Maritime Employers, 1973 (Box-folder 12/79)
      - ILWU Local 19/OEPEIU Local 8, 1987, 1996 (Box-folder 12/80)
      - ILWU Local 19/PMA, 1975-1998 (Box-folder 12/81-83)
      - ILWU Local 19/Port of Seattle, 1968-1997 (Box-folder 12/84)
      - ILWU Local 19/Drummond Lighterage, 1966 (Box-folder 12/85)
      - ILWU Local 19 Miscellaneous, 1997, n.d. (Box-folder 12/86)
      - ILWU Various Locals, 1967-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 12/87)
      - New York Longshore and Dock Agreement, 1954, 1957 (Box-folder 12/88)
      - Sublease-Foss Alaska, 1986 (Box-folder 12/89)
      - Toyota Auto Contract, 1971 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Working and Dispatch Rules, 1952-1988 (Box-folder 14/2-7)
    - Financial Reports, 1966-1998 (Box-folder 14/8-17)
    - Caucus and Convention Files (includes Minutes), 1958-1998 (Box-folder 14/18-34 to 15/1-29)
    - Subject Series
      - Banana Dock, 1955 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Bridges Letter, 1956, 1960 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - CIO Charges and Rebuttal, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Coda Phone, 1965 (Box-folder 16/4)
      - ILWU, 1955, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 16/5)
      - ILWU-PMA Welfare Fund, 1953-1968 (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Local 9, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 16/7)
      - Local 13 Wilmington Earning System Data, 1963 (Box-folder 16/8)
      - P.A. Travel, 1964 (Box-folder 16/9)
      - Petitions ... Short Gangs, n.d. (Box-folder 16/10)
      - Portland (Box-folder 16/11)
      - Portland Beef, June 1970 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Rule Changes for Bull Drivers, 1956 (Box-folder 16/13)
      - S/S Fortuna, 1964 (Box-folder 16/14)
      - Safety, 1967, n.d. (Box-folder 16/15)
      - Screening, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 16/16)
      - Special Caucus Velasquez, 1965 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Time Wage Loss Study, 1964 (Box-folder 16/18)
      - Velasquez, Pete, 1965, 1969 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - Publications
      - ILWU, 1951-1963 (Box-folder 16/20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1964, n.d. (Box-folder 16/21)
      - Maritime Strike Pictorial, 1937 (Box:oversize 34)
      - Maritime Reporter, 1961 (Box:oversize 34)
    - Newsletters
      - The Hook, 1950-1997 (Box-folder 16/22-23)
      - North Bend Breezes, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 16/24)
      - Waterfront Citizen, 1964 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Bulletins, 1950-1956, n.d. (Box-folder 16/26)
    - Speeches and Writings, 1961 (Box-folder 16/27)
    - Directories, 1967 (Box-folder 16/28)
    - Financial Records (of Proceedings), 1955-1965, n.d. (Box-folder 16/29)
    - Transcripts (of Proceedings)
      - ILWU Local 3 Trial, 1955 (Box-folder 16/30)
      - 1966 Caucus Excerpt (Box-folder 16/31)
    - Reports, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 16/32-34)
    - Legislation, 1957-1969 (Box-folder 16/35-36)
    - Regulations, 1969 (Box-folder 16/37)
    - News Releases, n.d. (Box-folder 16/38)
    - Petitions, n.d. (Box-folder 16/39)
    - Resolutions, 1957, n.d. (Box-folder 16/40)
    - Claims, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 16/41)
    - Claims of Others, 1962 (Box-folder 16/42)
    - Flyers, 1953-1967, n.d. (Box-folder 16/43-44)
    - Notes, 1964-1967, n.d. (Box-folder 16/45-48)
    - Miscellany, 1952-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 16/49-56)
    - Clippings, 1966 (Box-folder 16/57)
    - Block for Port Commissioner Committee
      - Invoices, 1965 (Box-folder 16/58)
      - Miscellany, 1965 (Box-folder 16/59)
    - Penalty Cargo Subcommittee
      - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 16/60)
      - Minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 16/61)
      - Agreements, 1967 (Box-folder 16/62-63)
      - Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 16/64, 17/1-7)
      - Transcripts, 1967 (Box-folder 17/8-9)
      - Reports, 1967 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Notes, 1966, n.d. (Box-folder 17/11-13)
    - Safety Subcommittee
      - Agreements, 1949, 1967 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 17/15-20)
      - Notes, 1967 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union. Local 19
    - Organizational Features
      - ILWU Constitution, 1971 (Box-folder 17/22)
      - Puget Sound Council, 1971 (Box-folder 17/23)
      - Amendments to Local 19 Constitution (Box-folder 17/24)
    - Incoming Letters
      - Bennet, Mike O., 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/25)
      - Bridges, Harry, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 17/26)
      - Grudin, D.A., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/27)
      - Huntsinger, Fred, 1970-1972, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17/28)
      - McMillan, J.A., 1972-1974 (Box-folder 17/29)
      - Schroeter, Leonard W., 1973-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 17/30)
      - Shields, James R., 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/31)
      - Ward, William T., 1965-1996, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/32)
      - Weber, Carl G., 1971-1976 (Box-folder 17/33)
      - A-G, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/34)
      - H-K, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/35)
      - L-O, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/36)
      - P-S, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/37)
      - T-Z, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/38)
      - Unidentified, 1971-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 17/39)
    - Outgoing Letters
      - Shields, James R. "J.R.", 1971-1974 (Box-folder 17/40)
      - Weber, Carl G. "C.G", 1972-1974 (Box-folder 17/41)
      - "Brothers" or "All Locals", 1963, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - A-D, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - E-L, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - M-Z, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 18/5-6)
      - Unidentified, 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 18/7)
    - General Correspondence
      - Alaska Steam / Western Steve[dore] - Pier 46, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - American Mail Lines / Western Stevedore Co., 1972 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Appenzeller, Muriel, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Benson, Henry A. Commissioner of Labor, Alaska Dept. of Labor, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Bentley, Helen Delieter, 1971 (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Bond - Port Angeles, 1973 (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Clark, Larry Apple Ships / Lauritzen Line, 1974 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Clark Letters, Peas, 1982 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Class "A," Low Hours, Welfare Eligibility, 1974 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Columbia Star, Western Steve., Horse Meat, 1974 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Container Movements and Data, 1973 (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Container Stevedoring Steady Men, 1972 (Box-folder 18/19)
      - Container Stevedoring Co., 1972 (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Crane Positions, 1972 (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Crescent Wharf & Warehouse Co., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 18/23)
      - Department of Labor and Industry re: Speeding on Docks, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Employers' Complaints, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 18/25-31)
      - Employers' Complaints Not Dealt With, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/32)
      - Forrester, William, 1971 (Box-folder 18/33)
      - Foss Alaska Lines - Pier 115, Safety on Car Racks, etc., 1974 (Box-folder 18/34)
      - Foss Alaska Lines - T. Letter Roll on Roll Off, 1974 (Box-folder 18/35)
      - Foss Launch & Tug Co., 1973 (Box-folder 18/36)
      - Foss Launch & Tug - Reliable Line Service Earnings, 1974 (Box-folder 18/37)
      - Fox, Frank, 1975 (Box-folder 18/38)
      - Fry, Howard, 1972 (Box-folder 18/39)
      - Grain Millers, Local 9, Krumm, 1974 (Box-folder 18/40)
      - Hoisting Pulp, Patent Slings Forrester Award, Cranston Co., OSHA, 1971, 1974 (Box-folder 18/41)
      - Howard, Joe S., 1965 (Box-folder 18/42)
      - Hulm, Bernard C. Alaska Report, Organization, 1975 (Box-folder 18/43)
      - Japanese Council Allied Enterprise Hydraulic Winches, n.d. (Box-folder 18/44)
      - Kagel Award, July 5, 1972 (Box-folder 18/45)
      - Krumm, Wilford, 1974 (Box-folder 18/46)
      - Levias, Nelson, 1973 (Box-folder 18/47)
      - Local 94, Foreman Contract, San Pedro, CA, n.d. (Box-folder 18/48)
      - Massey, Will Dept. Commissioner - U.S. Dept of Labor re: Employees Compensation, 1972 (Box-folder 18/49)
      - Meyers, Grant, 1975 (Box-folder 18/50)
      - Miniken, Don, 1967, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 18/51)
      - Miniken, Don to Gleason, 1974 (Box-folder 18/52)
      - Nickson, Roy, 1972 (Box-folder 18/53)
      - Pacific Molasses Co., 1971 (Box-folder 18/54)
      - Parks, John, 1971 (Box-folder 18/55)
      - Pension Qualifying Years 100 Hours etc. No Average, 1974 (Box-folder 18/56)
      - Pension Schedule, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 18/57)
      - Pensioners, 1972 (Box-folder 18/58)
      - Reliable Lines, 1975 (Box-folder 18/59)
      - Rental Costs PMA, 1972 (Box-folder 18/60)
      - Robot T-Manning, Kagel Decision on B/D, 1972 (Box-folder 18/61)
      - Ross, Rinaldi, Travelers Insurance, Sea Land, 1971 (Box-folder 18/62)
      - Runaway Containers and Freight Stations, 1975 (Box-folder 18/63)
      - Ryuko Maru - Sound, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/64)
      - Safety Engineers, G.E., Starporter Cranes, 1974 (Box-folder 18/65)
      - Scindia Steam Navigation Company, 1971 (Box-folder 18/66)
      - Sea-Land Injunction, 1975 (Box-folder 18/67)
      - Seattle. Port, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 18/68-72, 19/1)
      - Seattle. Port 19, 9, 1973 (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Seattle. Port / Captain Bennett, 1971 (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Smith, Mel Clarklift Straddles, 1974 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - SS Buckeye Atlantic / Buckeye Steamship Co., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/5)
      - SS Greenwave, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Straddle Trucks, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/7)
      - St. Germaine, Bill Straddle Trucks, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Tallow Manning, 1962 (Box-folder 19/9)
      - Tallow & Logs to Hook, Teamsters Under Gear & Hook, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19/10)
      - Tallow to Hook & Ship, Western Steve. 5/28/72, Crescent 11/19/71, 1967, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/11)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 1975 (Box-folder 19/12)
      - Butch Urhan, Training, 1974 (Box-folder 19/13)
      - Western Stevedore Company, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 19/14)
      - Western Steve. - Bum Equipment, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/15)
      - Western Steve. - Pier 25, 42 C.F.S., 1974 (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Western Steve. - APL - Pier 25 Continuous Operation Yard Bull, 1975 (Box-folder 19/17)
      - Western Steve. - Pier 25, Lift Truck Container in Yard, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Western Steve. - Steady Men Letters, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Draft Correspondence, 1973-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 19/20-21)
    - Correspondence of Others
      - ILWU International, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 19/22)
      - Local 19, 1975-1977, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 19/23)
      - Pacific Maritime Association (PMA), 1965, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 19/24)
      - Seattle. Port, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 19/25)
      - Various ILWU Locals, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 19/26)
      - A - R, 1970-1975, 1979 (Box-folder 19/27)
      - S - Z, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 19/28)
    - Minutes
      - Anacortes Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/29)
      - Bellingham Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 19/30)
      - Coast Labor Relations Committee, 1960-1975 (Box-folder 19/31-35)
      - Discussions with Local 19 re: 7 Day Dispatch and 6:00 pm start, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/36)
      - Everett Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/37)
      - Foreman's Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 19/38)
      - Grays Harbor, Port of, Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 19/39)
      - ILWU International Executive Board, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 19/40-41)
      - ILWU Jurisdictional Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 19/42)
      - ILWU Union Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 19/43)
      - ILWU Local 19 Disciplinary Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 19/44)
      - ILWU Local 19 Executive Board Meetings, 1969, 1971-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 19/45-46)
      - ILWU Local 19 Membership Meetings, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 19/47)
      - ILWU Local 19 Strike Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/48)
      - ILWU Local 19 Working Rules Negotiations, 1971 (Box-folder 19/49)
      - ILWU Local 52 Membership Meetings, 1971 (Box-folder 19/50)
      - ILWU Puget Sound Council, 1972, 1975 (Box-folder 19/51)
      - Joint Checker Labor Relations Committee of San Francisco, 1975 (Box-folder 19/52)
      - Joint ILWU - IUOE Meeting, 1974 (Box-folder 19/53)
      - Joint Labor Management Meetings, 1972 (Box-folder 19/54)
      - Joint Local Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 19/55)
      - Joint Port Labor Relations Committee for the Port of Tacoma, 1963, 1973 (Box-folder 19/56)
      - Meeting with Local 19 re: 7 Day Dispatch and Steady Men, 1972 (Box-folder 19/57)
      - Meeting with Sea-Land, 1971 (Box-folder 19/58)
      - Olympia Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 19/59)
      - Oregon Area Labor Relations Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 19/60)
      - Port Angeles Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 19/61)
      - Port Gamble Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 19/62)
      - Puget Sound Area Labor Relations Committee, 1951, 1963-1966, 1975 (Box-folder 19/63-64)
      - Safety Meetings, 1975 (Box-folder 19/65)
      - Seattle Clerks Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 19/66)
      - Seattle Clerks Joint Port Labor Relations Committee and Seattle Longshore Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 19/67)
      - Seattle Job Level Safety Committee, 1967 (Box-folder 19/68)
      - Seattle Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1960, 1965, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 19/69-73 to 20/1-4)
      - Seattle Mayor's Maritime Advisory Board, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 20/5)
      - Seattle. Port. ILWU Local 19 Labor Relations Committee, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 20/6)
      - Seattle. Port. Labor Management Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 20/7)
      - Seattle. Port. Port Commission Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 20/8)
      - Seattle Straddle Truck Joint Port Training & Promotions Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 20/9)
      - Special Union Area Labor Relations Meeting, n.d. (Box-folder 20/10)
      - Washington Area Joint Accident Prevention Committee, 1971, 1975 (Box-folder 20/11)
      - Washington Area Labor Relations Committee, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Washington Area Labor Relations Committee Draft Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 20/13)
      - Unidentified, 1972, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Agenda
      - Governor's 22nd Annual Safety Conference, 1971 (Box-folder 20/15)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor History Conference, n.d. (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Seattle Rank and File Labor Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Subject Series
      - 7-Day, n.d. (Box-folder 20/18)
      - 7-Day Dispatch, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box-folder 20/19)
      - 8 for 9 Hour Day, 1956 (Box-folder 20/20)
      - 9.43 - PMA, 1972 (Box-folder 20/21)
      - 1966 Contract - Dispatcher Supplement (Box-folder 20/22)
      - 1971 Strike (Box-folder 20/23)
      - Aetna Pensions, 1964, 1972, n.d. (Box-folder 20/24)
      - Alcohol, 1971 (Box-folder 20/25)
      - Alcohol Preventive Program, n.d. (Box-folder 20/26)
      - Alcoholic Program, n.d. (Box-folder 20/27)
      - Allende, Madame (Box-folder 20/28)
      - BALMA Local 10 Building, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 20/29)
      - Banana Dock, n.d. (Box-folder 20/30)
      - Bull Cooking, 1968, 1974 (Box-folder 20/31)
      - Cargill - Grain Dock Local Working Agreement, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 20/32)
      - Carrothers, Art, 1972 (Box-folder 20/33)
      - Chassis on Pier 25, 1973 (Box-folder 20/34)
      - Checkers, 1972 (Box-folder 20/35)
      - Clerks Data, 1 Day Turnover, Port of Seattle Arbitration 3/16/72, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 20/36)
      - Clerks' Test, 1973 (Box-folder 20/37)
      - Clerks on Turnover, 1967-1969, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/38)
      - Cold Storage Stairway Petition to City, 1972 (Box-folder 20/39)
      - Container Freight Stations OSHA v. State Compensation, 1974, 1976 (Box-folder 20/40)
      - Contract Vote 1975 (Box-folder 20/41)
      - Crane Positions Seattle, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 20/42)
      - Crane Training, 1973 (Box-folder 20/43)
      - Cutchlow - Williams, n.d. (Box-folder 20/44)
      - Data - S/L Actions, 1972 (Box-folder 20/45)
      - Dental Plan / Drug Plan, 1970 (Box-folder 20/46)
      - Disagreements Referred to the Area Labor Relations Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/47)
      - Dispatch Procedure, 1975 (Box-folder 20/48)
      - Don Page Original, 1973 (Box-folder 20/49)
      - Dues: Various Locals & 19 Costs, n.d. (Box-folder 20/50)
      - Duwamish Basin Development Committee - Phylis Lamphere (Box-folder 20/51)
      - Duwamish Project, n.d. (Box-folder 20/52)